hivehealthmedia.com 2018-08-24

# Hive Health Media Privacy Policy

**Hive Health Media** is committed to respecting the privacy concerns of its visitors to the **Hive Health media Network** (â€œthe Websitesâ€). Hive Health Media has created this privacy policy (the â€œPolicyâ€) to establish guidelines that will govern the collection, use, and disclosure of the personal and non-Personal Information of its visitors.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site.Â  These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see:Â  [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](https://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

Hive Health Media collects three kinds of information from the Websites: (1) your voluntarily provided Personal Information; (2) Anonymous Non-Personal Information; and (3) â€œCookieâ€ Based Information.

**Personal Information:** Hive Health Media does not automatically collect Personal Information, such as name, residential address, phone number, email address and other personally identifiable information, from its visitors (â€œPersonal Informationâ€). From time to time, Hive Health Media will collect Personal Information that is voluntarily provided by its visitors in filling out contest entry forms and subscribing to newsletters and other activities carried out on the Websites. Hive Health Media will only collect, use and disclose Personal Information after the visitor has voluntarily agreed to such collection, use and disclosure. Hive Health Media also sometimes use email addresses that have been voluntarily provided by its visitors to respond to visitors who communicate with us, to inform winners of contests or to allow subscription to newsletters and other services. All emails from Hive Health Media to its visitors include instructions on how to discontinue receipt of emails, newsletters and other communication from Hive Health Media and visitors can discontinue such communication at any time. Email addresses from visitors who wish to discontinue receipt of Hive Health Mediaâ€™s emails will be removed from Hive Health Mediaâ€™s distribution lists. All Personal Information that may identify a visitor and has been collected with the visitorâ€™s consent by Hive Health Media is not disclosed in any identifiable form to any other party outside the company except for the fulfillment of the specific purpose identified to the visitor at the time of collection, or as may be required by law.

Hive Health Media may disclose such information in anonymous, aggregated and non-personally identifiable form to other parties for marketing, advertising or other purposes and to better understand visitorâ€™s use of the Website. At any time, a visitor may send an email to admin@hivehealthmedia.com to request that Personal Information be reviewed, changed, removed or updated in Hive Health Mediaâ€™s databases.

Visitors should exercise caution when they disclosed personally Personal Information in comments to blog sites, on bulletin boards or chat rooms on the Websites or any other website. Such areas are accessible by anyone and may result in the visitor receiving unsolicited messages from other people and/or companies. Although Hive Health Media is committed to protecting the Personal Information provided to it by its visitors in compliance with this Privacy Policy, it cannot guarantee the security of information, whether personal or otherwise, that visitors disclose online to publicly accessible bulletin boards or chat rooms.

**Notice Regarding Online Behavioral Advertising: Â  **We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visitÂ [www.networkadvertising.org](https://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**Anonymous Non-Personal Information:** When visitors visit the Websites, anonymous, non Personal Information about their visit is automatically collected. Such information may include the length and date of the visit, how the visitor navigated the Websites, what pages the visitor viewed, the type of browser being used by the visitor, the type of operating system used by the visitor and the domain name of the visitorâ€™s Internet service provider. Hive Health Media uses this Anonymous Non-Personal Information to track the success of its Websites with its visitors and to better tailor the Websites to visitorsâ€™ needs and interests. This Anonymous Non-Personal Information may be shared with other parties, such as broadcasters, advertisers, sponsors and partners.

**Cookie-Based Information:** Hive Health Media may use cookies on its Websites. â€œCookiesâ€ are pieces of information that a website transfers to a visitorâ€™s hard drive for record keeping and identification purposes. Cookies are used to make the visitorâ€™s use of a website easier by saving visitor preferences and passwords and to identify which areas of the website are popular and which areas need improvement and how to target certain advertising to its visitors. Hive Health Media does not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information except in connection with a password protected online registration for a contest or newsletter or other service and only with the visitorâ€™s informed consent. Visitors may visit the Websites with its cookies turned off to avoid the collection of Cookie-based Information.

**Protection of Visitorsâ€™ Personal Information:** Hive Health Media protects the Personal Information it collects with appropriate technological (firewall, password protected servers), physical and administrative safeguards to protect it from unauthorized disclosure or use. Access to Personal Information collected by Hive Health Media is limited to authorized individuals. Hive Health Media retains the Personal Information only for as long as is required for the purposes identified at the time of its collection and consented to by the visitor providing it or as otherwise required by law. Once Personal Information is no longer necessary for the purposes consented to by the visitor, Hive Health Media will delete it from its data bases or make it anonymous.

**Linked Websites:** The Websites may have links to other websites. These linked websites are not under the control of Hive Health Media. Visitors should ensure that they read and understand how their Personal Information may be collected, used, and disclosed by the linked websites as Hive Health Media is not responsible for and shall not be held liable for any procedures, policies or activities of any websites linked to the Websites.

**Visitorâ€™s Consent to Privacy Policy:** By visiting and using the Websites, the visitor agrees to the Privacy Policy and the Terms of Use included with this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with the Privacy Policy or Terms of Use, do not use the Websites or provide Personal Information.

Hive Health Media is compliant with the federal Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (â€œPIPEDAâ€). Hive Health Media takes compliance with the ten principles set out in the â€œModel Code for the Protection of Personal Informationâ€ which is included in PIPEDA â€“ a summary of which is set out below.

**TEN PRINCIPLES OF FAIR INFORMATION PRACTICES**

PRINCIPLE 1 â€“ ACCOUNTABILITY

Hive Health Media is responsible for the Personal Information under its control and shall designate one or more individuals who shall be accountable for the companyâ€™s compliance with the procedures and principles set out in this Privacy Policy and relevant legislation. As such Hive Health Media has appointed a member of its management team as its Privacy Officer, who is responsible for reviewing, approving and administering this Privacy Policy and Hive Health Mediaâ€™s commitments hereunder. If you have any questions, concerns or comments, feel free to contact the Privacy Officer at admin@hivehealthmedia.com.

PRINCIPLE 2 â€“ IDENTIFYING PURPOSE

Hive Health Media will identify the purpose for which Personal Information is collected at or before the time the information is collected. The purposes for which information is collected, used or disclosed by Hive Health Media must be those that a reasonable person would consider are appropriate in the circumstances.

PRINCIPLE 3 â€“ CONSENT

The knowledge and consent of the individual are required for the collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information, except where consent is not required by law.

PRINCIPLE 4 â€“ LIMITING COLLECTION

Hive Health Media shall limit the collection of personal information to that which is necessary for the purposes identified. Personal Information will only be collected by fair and lawful means.

PRINCIPLE 5 â€“ LIMITING USE, DISCLOSURE AND RETENTION

Personal Information will not be used or disclosed for purposes other than those for which it was collected, except with the consent of the individual or as required by law. Personal Information will be retained only as long as necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which it was collected.

PRINCIPLE 6 â€“ ACCURACY

Personal Information will be as accurate, complete and up-to-date as is necessary for the purposes for which it is to be used.

PRINCIPLE 7 â€“ SAFEGUARDS

Personal Information shall be protected by security safeguards appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. See â€œProtection of Visitorsâ€™ Personal Informationâ€ for more detail.

PRINCIPLE 8 â€“ OPENNESS

Hive Health Media will make readily available to its Visitors specific information about its policies and practices relating to the management of personal information.

PRINCIPLE 9 â€“ INDIVIDUAL ACCESS

Upon request, an individual will be informed of the existence, use and disclosure of his or her personal information and will be given access to that information, except where Hive Health Media may be permitted or required by law not to disclose personal information to the individual. An individual will be able to challenge the accuracy and completeness of the information disclosed to him or her and have it be amended as appropriate.

PRINCIPLE 10 â€“ CHALLENGING COMPLIANCE

An individual Visitor will be able to address a challenge concerning compliance with the principles in this Privacy Policy to Hive Health Mediaâ€™s webmaster. Hive Health Media will investigate any complaint, and if the complaint is justified, Hive Health Media will remedy it.
